Last time on Zombieland Saga, we ran out of money even though we haven't really done anything yet.
Which is why we decided to accept our first offer for a paid appearance.
And it was at a hot spring!
We even got to take in the sights around town and have some fun!
The show was awesome, and we snuck into the bath even though we weren't supposed to.
A girl's gotta celebrate, right?
Let's just say we weren't very discreet, and our chance at a partnership was dead on arrival.
Partially my fault, I guess.
Sorry, guys!
Time to play ball!
It's the championship game to determine the Ultimate Idol team!
We're now in the ninth inning with three runs apiece!
Will Team Franshu-shu be able to hold it together against the competitor?
Here comes their race pitcher, Saki Nekaito!
Huh?
Just kidding, I'm gonna pitch instead!
Oh yeah!
HOME RUN!
DARE YOU TO TRY THAT AGAIN, PRICK!
There!
Um, sir?
What are you doing on the floor?
Sweeping up my dignity!
The old diamond is a cruel mistress!
You let your guard down for a second, you strike out!
Oh, okay.
The point is, you better not slack off, or you'll be in real trouble, you undead stupid heads!
Did you forget your little mishap?
You spilled da brains!
Uh...
Right.
We want idle buzz, not zombie buzz!
Thanks to you, our budget's been disemboweled!
You're the one spending money, so...
Say what you want, but your illustrious manager has secured a gig for you that's such an easy home run, even you slobs can't blow it!
We need to start boosting our profile, so the logical thing to do is appear in a commercial spot for an extremely well-known and successful business here in Saga.
Wow, you mean we're getting offers for commercials now?
That's how I do, babe.
And when you hear who it is, it might just shock you back to life!
Are you ready?
The business in question is none other than...
The Famous Drive-In Toriii!
I lower the complaint blame?
Where are you working!
Fizze...
What's the name?
You
Holy crap. It really is driving, Toddy.
Driving who?
You don't know?
Respect the gods of chicken or you're undead meat.
I'm sorry, okay.
I've heard of it, but I've never been.
What the hell?
All you punks fail at Saga!
Is it that great?
Well, you can form your own opinion.
We'll be shooting it very soon.
Really? When do we start?
We start right now!
Well, it definitely has a mom and pop feel, doesn't it?
This is the famous place?
It's just like coming home again.
Sure takes me back.
When I was alive, me and my girls used to spend all day and night raising hell.
And afterwards, we'd hit drive-in Toddy for late night eats.
I remember the number one yakitori meal was our go-to for the big side of lettuce.
You had a pretty wild lifestyle, huh, Saki?
That chicken's kind of grody.
Your face is going to be grody if you keep talking crap about Coco!
Coco, huh?
What's the holdup?
Look alive, deadbeats!
Say hello to the esteemed president of Drive-in Toddy.
It's nice to make your acquaintance.
Hello, Sam.
This is a huge honor!
Jeez, weirdo.
I appreciate you coming today.
I'm really looking forward to seeing what you bring to the table for our advertising campaign.
Let's go in so you can sample our signature grilled chicken.
That sounds great!
I'm not worthy!
Most people tend to think of beef when it comes to yakiniku-style grilling,
but in Saga Prefecture, it's all about chicken.
Hey, Sakura, try some of that sauce with the garlic pepper.
Ooh, this is a good piece.
Hey!
I was poking that for me, big baby!
You should take that one, Ralee.
It's already well done.
What are you looking at there, Lady Shunko?
Says they have a honey and black vinegar cactus.
Bet that's good.
What?
Those are the seven basic principles of our company.
Oh.
Hey, would it kill you to listen up?
It's all right, really.
I'm just happy to see that they're enjoying the food so much.
Yeah, it really is incredible.
Thank you.
That's great to hear.
All the chicken we serve is fresh and...
I know!
It's not safe to eat it wrong!
Oh!
Hey, I said it's fresh, but not that fresh!
Now then, let's talk about what you want from that chute.
Woo-hoo!
The one time we don't have to wear t-shirts and they put us in these.
But this will help pay for better outfits.
That looks so great on you, Junko!
Don't lie to me.
You look adorable!
This would have been perfect in my previous line of work.
All right, everybody, it's time to get this show on the road!
First off, I'd like to introduce you to our lovely new singers for our commercial,
from Shushu!
Of course, we also have our beloved mascot,
Give It Up for Coco!
Coco!
We're in the presence of true greatness!
Just breathe!
Yeah, you're getting creepy.
Um, sorry, sir!
Back off!
You can't eat Coco!
They told me not to say this, but that's just a guy in a suit!
Hmm, hmm, hmm, hmm!
Now, if everybody's ready, I say we go ahead and work through the first take!
Let's rock!
Thanks for having us!
And we won't let you down!
This'll be a dry run!
And action!
Action!
Try the yuck and tori plate, or a chicken rice bowl,
Healthy and delicious salads, too!
Great service with a smile!
Stop by and stay a while!
Yay!
Cut!
Uh, is there something wrong with the vocals?
Mm-hmm.
We'll fix it.
Sing better!
Saki, stop.
You know she can't do it.
What should we do?
You ready?
Well, I'm not sure.
Just cut out all of that demonic growling, and it'll be perfect.
Rolling!
Wait, we're not!
We're all set, guys!
Okay, here's the plan.
You just do the cock-a-doodle-doo at the end, Ty.
Ugh.
This one's for real.
Second take!
Yeah!
Ready?
Go!
Yeah!
Cut!
Yeah, cut!
I'm sorry!
Let's do a quick check and move on.
It was a great idea to change the harmony at the end.
That works.
He is downright obsessed with it!
That's such a relief.
I'm not sure I agree.
You really think you nailed that?
Um...
Look at yourselves.
What exactly are you girls supposed to be?
Idols, I think.
You're chickens!
This place serves chicken!
Am I right or wrong?
You're right!
You have to be so much more chicken-y!
Crank that squawking chicken energy up to 11!
I need to be able to picture you sizzling on top of a tabletop grill!
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
Your job!
For once, I think I might agree with him.
Huh?
Guys, we failed.
They wanted real chickens and we blew it!
But that tape was okay.
I know you're stupid, but I promise you they can do this!
Please, just one more chance!
I mean, look!
Come on, you don't want to let Coco show us up, do you?
If we're going to take over all of Japan, we've got to be able to gobble up the star of the whole show!
I know!
Somebody stop her!
Hurry!
Yes, sir!
Wait!
Roll that camera!
This is reality!
This is the story we never knew we needed to see!
Stop!
She didn't see!
We should literally be chickens!
Say the word!
Action!
Oh!
Great job with the commercial.
You were so into it.
This is our way of showing our gratitude.
You think it's food?
T-shirts.
More T-shirts.
I'm excited to see the final product.
Hmm?
Hmm.
Hey, that's a new ad.
Local idols, huh?
Must be hard to do that in Saga.
Have I seen that girl before?
Good job, girls!
You make some nice birds!
Real nice birds!
I serve you, but it's a new diet.
T-shirts!
I still need to recognize it, too!
Thank you.
Si.
Bonjour, Saga Jeune.
What?
Cause you're in Saga.
Yeah, I guess I am a Saga Jeune now.
What makes you a Saga Jeune?
What's with you?
There he goes.
Listen up!
The way you are right now,
not one of you snot-wiping loser zombies
gets to call yourself a Saga Jeune.
But I've come up with a way
to turn you into Saga Jeunes
who could rival the fair Mademoiselle Zeperri.
Time for the Gat-Olympics!
No way, man.
We get to compete?
Crying again?
You do know anyone can enter that, right?
What even is it, though?
You don't know?
All of you fail at Saga-
Ew, gross.
It's not very glamorous, is it?
Yeah, I don't wanna.
Too bad!
That is the ugliest freaking shirt I've ever seen.
Like it or not,
you ladies will each be sporting one of these
while you're competing in the Gat-Olympics.
Sounds good.
When is it, though?
It's right now!
This kind of reminds me of those swimsuit-only sporting events
they used to have.
You actually entered those things?
Yes, but I always wore tasteful ones.
I do not like this.
We need them for advertising.
You'll have to bear it.
Hold still.
You're gonna rip it.
It's almost a cutoff time for sign-up.
Anyone who would like to resist-
It's about to start.
Come on, there's gotta be an extra T-shirt in here.
Oh, I know.
Let's put another layer on you
so you don't tear this one.
Hey, aren't those the girls
from that new chicken commercial?
Okobo, you duck.
You know they're way out of your league.
Don't be stupid.
Hmm.
I still can't figure out
why she's so familiar.
It's time for the headline event
of the Gat-Olympics Mudbiking!
Let's see who can ride their bicycles
all the way across!
Okay!
First up, we have a courageous officer
from our very own Saga PD
here to show us how it's done!
Do you have a comment?
Uh, yeah!
You know, I'm just here to represent, uh,
world peace!
What an inspiring message!
Now, on your mark, get set!
And that's all there is to it!
Good luck, competitors!
You sure you'll be awesome, Saki?
Hell yeah!
Give me two wheels and I'm unstoppable!
It's time to kick off the first race!
Eat my dust, suckers!
On your mark, get set!
Let's move on to the next group!
You can't even see what's on the T-shirts anymore!
I totally saw this coming!
I don't know!
You can't even see what's on the T-shirts anymore!
It's time to see what's on the T-shirts anymore!
I don't know!
I don't know what you're saying!
Now you can read what they say!
Hey!
Can't catch me!
Wait for me!
I just made a huge mistake!
Well, this is a bit of a disappointment.
Next up, we have...
Uh, Kotaro Tatsumi.
You're kidding!
And he's not even wearing one of our t-shirts.
Do you have a comment?
Oh, he can give us a shout-out!
I'll, uh, try my best.
And?
Um, that's it.
What the hell?!
Well, at least we can laugh our asses off when he gets a face full of mud!
On your marks, get set!
Show me!
This next event is arguably more challenging than the last!
We call it the Tarzan Mud Swing!
It's all you, Officer!
It's time for me to become one with...
The Aria DC!
Alley!
There you have it!
Scores are based on a combination of distance and showmanship!
Who cares how well we do if they can't read our t-shirts?
You have a point.
Perhaps if we make it over there, we can attract some more attention.
Forget about the shirts!
That looks like a way better idea to me!
Hell yeah!
We should aim straight for those weird block thingies!
This is our best shot, ladies!
Here comes our next contestant!
If anyone can do this, I think it'll be her!
Total distance, 5 meters and 20 centimeters!
Not very impressive!
They aren't even cheering!
This is higher up than I thought!
Block thingies, here I come!
Total distance, 3 meters!
Wow, nice going!
Oh yeah!
Get that rope hair, you kitty!
I'll try!
Oh!
Zero meters, but the aesthetic value puts her ahead!
Here it goes!
Magical!
Do it in!
Zero meters, but the aesthetic value puts her ahead!
Here it goes!
Magical!
Do it in!
Stop!
Now that's what I call distance!
That puts her in fourth place!
Not quite enough to reach the podium, though!
Oh!
Oh I'm going faster.
What a little clutch! Even I could've done it better than she did.
I'm sure.
Yeah, this ain't gonna work.
Huh! Now this girl's got a unique style!
It's Tai!
That's a... something? Hard to tell what happened with the sunshine, but it looked pretty gnarly.
This is bad! We got a finger!
Whoa! We're giving the best hands of the month a helper! What a stunning display of camaraderie!
And now we'll have a quick interview with the winner!
What we just saw was an incredible victory! So, how does it feel?
So much for Idol Buzz.
I guess so.
Oops, I think she's still got too much mud in her mouth to talk. Anyway, you were amazing! Congratulations!
Oh, well. What's done is done.
Hold on. Tai's wearing two shirts.
She is?
Hey! Take off your outside shirt!
Let's get another hair!
Take off your outside!
Attraventory!
Nice bird!
They really are an adorable bunch of girls, huh?
Hey, wait a minute. I remember now.
Remember what?
I should look into this.
This is I. Whether it's clucking like chickens or rolling in mud, we're doing whatever it takes to get Saga's attention.
Next time on Zombieland Saga Episode 6, because it's Sentimental Saga. Don't miss it!